

ABOUT ME

I've been interested in coding since middle school, where I started out by coding some simple scripts and games in BASIC. Now, my technical skillset includes over four years of academic and self-taught experience with several programming languages, frameworks, and other aspects of computer science.

I've also worked in the IT field, in which I've gained valuable experience working with end users and honing my general troubleshooting skills. I love learning new things and am eager to join your team!

CONTACT

PHONE:

+1-314-835-0097

EMAIL:

treynolds3610@gmail.com

LINKS

WEBSITE:

http://thomasreynoldscode.com

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/thomasreynolds-212917104/

GITHUB:

https://github.com/thomasreynolds48

THOMAS REYNOLDS

Technical Talent

EDUCATION

Drake University

August 2018 – May 2022 B.S. Computer Science / Data Analytics

WORK EXPERIENCE

Covetrus – IT Technician

June 2021-August 2021

Staged printers and workstations for a new Warehouse Management System. Provided remote support for different distribution centers.

Drake University ITS - IT Help Desk

August 2020–May 2022

Took phone calls and responded to tickets, troubleshooted issues remotely and directly with end users.

PROJECTS

GiveMeFilm - Movie Recommendation Website

Worked with a team to develop a website that would generate movie recommendations for users. Utilized a React frontend and a Flask backend, with MongoDB Atlas to store data. PyTest for unit testing.

Habitat for Humanity – Case Study

Developed a simple React app to quickly estimate the cost of a given Habitat for Humanity project using a GLM generated in R.

Bank Failure Research

Automated the process of cleaning and adding data to a MySQL database using Python. The data was used to answer machine learning questions regarding historic bank failure.

SKILLS

